<AinesmileLanguage name="forth" pattern="" suffix="forth" comment_line="\" comment_start="(" comment_end=")">
	<keyword name="instre1">AGAIN BEGIN CASE DO ELSE ENDCASE ENDOF IF LOOP OF REPEAT THEN UNTIL WHILE [IF] [ELSE] [THEN] ?DO</keyword>
	<keyword name="instre2">DUP DROP ROT SWAP OVER @ ! 2@ 2! 2DUP 2DROP 2SWAP 2OVER NIP R@ &gt;R R&gt; 2R@ 2&gt;R 2R&gt; 0= 0&lt; SP@ SP! W@ W! C@ C! &lt; &gt; = &lt;&gt; 0&lt;&gt;SPACE SPACES KEY? KEY THROW CATCH ABORT */ 2* /MOD CELL+ CELLS CHAR+ CHARS MOVE ERASE DABS TITLE HEX DECIMAL HOLD &lt;# # #S #&gt; SIGN D. . U. DUMP (.&quot;) &gt;NUMBER &apos; IMMEDIATE EXIT RECURSE UNLOOP LEAVE HERE ALLOT , C, W, COMPILE, BRANCH, RET, LIT, DLIT, ?BRANCH, &quot;, &gt;MARK &gt;RESOLVE1 &lt;MARK &gt;RESOLVE ALIGN ALIGNED USER-ALLOT USER-HERE HEADER DOES&gt; SMUDGE HIDE :NONAME LAST-WORD ?ERROR ERROR2 FIND1 SFIND SET-CURRENT GET-CURRENT DEFINITIONS GET-ORDER FORTH ONLY SET-ORDER ALSO PREVIOUS VOC-NAME. ORDER LATEST LITERAL 2LITERAL SLITERAL CLITERAL ?LITERAL1 ?SLITERAL1 HEX-LITERAL HEX-SLITERAL ?LITERAL2 ?SLITERAL2 SOURCE EndOfChunk CharAddr PeekChar IsDelimiter GetChar OnDelimiter SkipDelimiters OnNotDelimiter SkipWord SkipUpTo ParseWord NextWord PARSE SKIP CONSOLE-HANDLES REFILL DEPTH ?STACK ?COMP WORD INTERPRET BYE QUIT MAIN1 EVALUATE INCLUDE-FILE INCLUDED &gt;BODY +WORD WORDLIST CLASS! CLASS@ PAR! PAR@ ID. ?IMMEDIATE ?VOC IMMEDIATE VOC WordByAddrWl WordByAddr NLIST WORDS SAVE OPTIONS /notransl ANSI&gt;OEM ACCEPT EMIT CR TYPE EKEY? EKEY EKEY&gt;CHAR EXTERNTASK ERASE-IMPORTS ModuleName ModuleDirName ENVIRONMENT? DROP-EXC-HANDLER SET-EXC-HANDLER HALT ERR CLOSE-FILE CREATE-FILE CREATE-FILE-SHARED OPEN-FILE-SHARED DELETE-FILE FILE-POSITION FILE-SIZE OPEN-FILE READ-FILE REPOSITION-FILE DOS-LINES UNIX-LINES READ-LINE WRITE-FILE RESIZE-FILE WRITE-LINE ALLOCATE FREE RESIZE START SUSPEND RESUME STOP PAUSE MIN MAX TRUE FALSE ASCIIZ&gt; R/O W/O ;CLASS ENDWITH OR AND /STRING SEARCH COMPARE EXPORT ;MODULE SPACE</keyword>
	<keyword name="type1">VARIABLE CREATE : VALUE CONSTANT VM: M: var dvar chars OBJ CONSTR: DESTR: CLASS: OBJECT: POINTER USER USER-CREATE USER-VALUE VECT WNDPROC: VOCABULARY -- TASK: CEZ: MODULE:</keyword>
	<keyword name="type2">CHAR [CHAR] POSTPONE WITH [&apos;] TO [COMPILE] CHAR ASCII \&apos;</keyword>
	<keyword name="type3">REQUIRE WINAPI</keyword>
	<keyword name="type4">S&quot; ABORT&quot; Z&quot; &quot; .&quot; C&quot;</keyword>
</AinesmileLanguage>

